<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">FragmentiStrbad</string>
    <string name="picture10_title">IC2944: The Running Chicken Nebula</string>
    <string name="picture10_desc">To some, it looks like a giant chicken running across the sky. To others, it looks like a gaseous nebula where star formation takes place. Cataloged as IC 2944, the Running Chicken Nebula spans about 100 light years and lies about 6,000 light years away toward the constellation of the Centaur (Centaurus).  The featured image, shown in scientifically assigned colors, was captured recently in a 16-hour exposure over three nights. The star cluster Collinder 249 is visible embedded in the nebula\'s glowing gas.  Although difficult to discern here, several dark molecular clouds with distinct shapes can be found inside the nebula.</string>
    <string name="picture11_title">North Star: Polaris and Surrounding Dust</string>
    <string name="picture11_desc">Why is Polaris called the North Star? First, Polaris is the nearest bright star toward the north spin axis of the Earth.  Therefore, as the Earth turns, stars appear to revolve around Polaris, but Polaris itself always stays in the same northerly direction -- making it the North Star.  Since no bright star is near the south spin axis of the Earth, there is currently no bright South Star.  Thousands of years ago, Earth\'s spin axis pointed in a slightly different direction so that Vega was the North Star.  Although Polaris is not the brightest star on the sky, it is easily located because it is nearly aligned with two stars in the cup of the Big Dipper. Polaris is near the center of the eight-degree wide featured image, a digital composite of hundreds of exposures that brings out faint gas and dust of the Integrated Flux Nebula (IFN) all over the frame as well as the globular star cluster NGC 188 on the far left.  The surface of Cepheid Polaris slowly pulsates, causing the famous star to change its brightness by a few percent over the course of a few days.    Explore Your Universe: Random APOD Generator</string>
    <string name="picture12_title">NGC 206 and the Star Clouds of Andromeda</string>
    <string name="picture12_desc">The large stellar association cataloged as NGC 206 is nestled within the dusty arms of the neighboring Andromeda galaxy along with the galaxy\'s pinkish star-forming regions. Also known as M31, the spiral galaxy is a mere 2.5 million light-years away. NGC 206 is found right of center in this sharp and detailed close-up of the southwestern extent of Andromeda\'s disk. The bright, blue stars of NGC 206 indicate its youth. In fact, its youngest massive stars are less than 10 million years old. Much larger than the open or galactic clusters of young stars in the disk of our Milky Way galaxy, NGC 206 spans about 4,000 light-years. That\'s comparable in size to the giant stellar nurseries NGC 604 in nearby spiral M33 and the Tarantula Nebula in the Large Magellanic Cloud.</string>
    <string name="picture13_title">NGC 2419: Intergalactic Wanderer</string>
    <string name="picture13_desc">Stars of the globular cluster NGC 2419 are packed into this Hubble Space Telescope field of view toward the mostly stealthy constellation Lynx. The two brighter spiky stars near the edge of the frame are within our own galaxy. NGC 2419 itself is remote though, some 300,000 light-years away. In comparison, the Milky Way\'s satellite galaxy, the Large Magellanic Cloud, is only about 160,000 light-years distant. Roughly similar to other large globular star clusters like Omega Centauri, NGC 2419 is intrinsically bright, but appears faint because it is so far away. Its extreme distance makes it difficult to study and compare its properties with other globular clusters that roam the halo of our Milky Way galaxy. Sometimes called \\\"the Intergalactic Wanderer\\\", NGC 2419 really does seem to have come from beyond the Milky Way. Measurements of the cluster\'s motion through space suggest it once belonged to the Sagittarius dwarf spheroidal galaxy, another small satellite galaxy being disrupted by repeated encounters with the much larger Milky Way.</string>
    <string name="picture14_title">Portrait of NGC 3628</string>
    <string name="picture14_desc">Sharp telescopic views of NGC 3628 show a puffy galactic disk divided by dark dust lanes. Of course, this portrait of the magnificent, edge-on spiral galaxy puts some astronomers in mind of its popular moniker, the Hamburger Galaxy. It also reveals a small galaxy nearby (below), likely a satellite of NGC 3628, and a very faint but extensive tidal tail. The drawn out tail stretches for about 300,000 light-years, even beyond the left edge of the frame. NGC 3628 shares its neighborhood in the local universe with two other large spirals M65 and M66 in a grouping otherwise known as the Leo Triplet. Gravitational interactions with its cosmic neighbors are likely responsible for creating the tidal tail, as well as the extended flare and warp of this spiral\'s disk. The tantalizing island universe itself is about 100,000 light-years across and 35 million light-years away in the northern springtime constellation Leo.</string>
    <string name="open_webpage">Open in web browser</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="power_connected">Power connected</string>
    <string name="power_disconnected">Power disconnected</string>
    <string name="unknown_action">Unknown action</string>
    <string name="share_message">Do you want to share this picture?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>